http://www.cie.ca/privacy

Schedule
Questions?
Jobs
OverviewCIE Learning, LLC (“CIE”, “we”, “us” or “our”) is committed to protecting the privacy of all information individuals share with us.Amendments to this Privacy Policy will be posted here, and will be effective when posted.Information Collection, Usage, and RetentionWe only collect and retain information that you have knowingly submitted to us by filling out a website form, or by sending us an email.We do not provide your information to third-party services except for payment processing as outlined below.When you enroll in one of our programs, we ask for personal information that will be used to validate your enrollment, and allow us to communicate with you for the purposes set out below. Your name, address, telephone number, email address, and user name will be securely stored in our records.At the conclusion of our in-person seminars, we ask if participants would like to share a contact list of all participant's names and email addresses. You may opt-out of this, or choose to modify or remove your information shared with fellow participants at any time.Only employees who need access to your personal information to fulfill their duties or to provide you with assistance have access to it.We do not knowingly collect personal information from anyone under 16 years of age.We endeavor to keep unsolicited communication with you to an absolute minimum. However we may use your information for the following purposes (subject to your opt-out rights outlined in this Privacy Policy):To provide customer service.To inform you of new programs or services available, or changes any programs or services we provide.To improve the quality of our website and programs through occasional surveys.To protect against fraud or error, and to respond to claims of any violation of our rights.As required to comply with applicable laws or as authorized by applicable laws.Your personal information may be stored and accessed in any country where we have offices. By using the our programs, you consent to the transfer of information to countries outside your country of residence, which may have different data protection rules than in your country.However, our practices regarding your personal information will at all times continue to be governed by this Privacy Policy and we will comply with the General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”) requirements.We will strive to prevent unauthorized access to your personal information, however, no data transmission over the Internet, by wireless device or over the air is guaranteed to be 100% secure. We have implemented and maintain reasonable security procedures and practices to protect that information from unauthorized disclosure. We will maintain your personal information for as long as they are needed, or as required by applicable laws, regulations, or government orders.Payment ProcessingWe do not store usable credit card information, however for the purposes of billing we utilizes third-party payment gateways, such as Stripe, Square, and Paypal, who will utilize your credit card and other payment information in accordance with their respective privacy policies. We shall not be liable to you or any other person for any damages that might result from unauthorized use, publication, disclosure or other misuse of such payment information.Opting-OutAt anytime, upon request, you have the right to have all stored personal information permanently cleared from our records.At anytime, you have the right to request that we cease to communicate with you.On the occasion when we communicate with you regarding our products, services, news and events, you will also be given the option to no longer receive such information.It may take 48-72 hours to comply with such requests.Rights to Your InformationAt anytime, you have the right to access and edit your information. Upon request and subject to proof of identity, you may view the personal information that we hold, and ask that any necessary corrections or deletions be made.It may take 48-72 hours to comply with such requests.Under the GDPR, you may be entitled to additional rights. If you want to learn more about your rights under the GDPR, you can visit the European Commission’s page on Data Protection.Cookies and Log FilesWe use cookies and log files to track user information. Cookies are small amounts of data that are transferred to your web browser by a web server and are stored on your computer’s hard drive. We use cookies to track which page variant a visitor has seen, to track if a visitor has clicked on a page variant, to monitor traffic patterns and to gauge popularity of service options. We will use this information to deliver relevant content and services to you.Change of Ownership or Business TransitionIn the event of a change of ownership or other business transition, such as a merger, acquisition or sale of our assets, your information may be transferred in accordance with applicable privacy laws.Contact UsIf you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, or to make a request to access or modify your information, or to exercise any applicable rights, we can be reached at admin@cie.ca or 818-514-5158.
Privacy Policy
Terms
×
Notice
Close
